{
    "id": "c7cf629d340948c09b7763b13db5cdea",
    "title": "Easily Confused Words Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9de4a43d7f094a21a029dc4721b9b22e",
            "title": "Easily Confused Words Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The cold weather .............................. my health.",
                    "description": "Affect is a verb and effect is a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "affected",
                        "effected"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The cold weather had an adverse .............................. on my health.",
                    "description": "Affect is a verb and effect is a noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "affect",
                        "effect"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Travel can be an excellent ................................. to one's education.",
                    "description": "A complement is something that completes.",
                    "answers": [
                        "complement",
                        "compliment"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The hostess received glowing ............................... on the dinner.",
                    "description": "A compliment is an expression of praise.",
                    "answers": [
                        "complements",
                        "compliments"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The extreme cold................................ the mountain climbers.",
                    "description": "To discomfort is to make someone uncomfortable.",
                    "answers": [
                        "uncomforted",
                        "miscomforted",
                        "discomforted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I made ............................... inquiries about his credit rating.",
                    "description": "Discreet means careful, judicious or cautious.",
                    "answers": [
                        "discreet",
                        "discrete"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Use your own .................................. in choosing a restaurant.",
                    "description": "Discretion means good judgment.",
                    "answers": [
                        "discreetion",
                        "discretion",
                        "discreation"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Charles Dickens was an .................................. writer.",
                    "description": "Eminent means illustrious.",
                    "answers": [
                        "eminent",
                        "imminent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "A storm is ...............................",
                    "description": "Imminent means impending.",
                    "answers": [
                        "eminent",
                        "imminent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Not even the experts could figure out the magician's ............................ escape.",
                    "description": "Ingenious means clever, cunning.",
                    "answers": [
                        "ingenious",
                        "ingenuous"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Children are more ........................................... than adults.",
                    "description": "Ingenuous means open or frank.",
                    "answers": [
                        "ingenious",
                        "ingenuous"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ................................. credit cards here.",
                    "description": "To accept is to take something offered.",
                    "answers": [
                        "accept",
                        "agree",
                        "expect"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}